

Tristan DeAugustine

Full-Stack Software Developer

Experienced Developer from St Petersburg with a demonstrated history of working hard and dedicating time to my passion for code. Strong engineering professional with a Full Stack Software Development focused in Front End from Suncoast Developers Guild. Aside from software development you can probably find me writing music or spending time with my friends and family.

deaugustinetristan@gmail.com

941-720-7443



10600 4th st n, St Petersburg, United States

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teachers Assistant Suncoast Developers Guild

10/2019 - Present

Full-Stack software developer bootcamp Achievements/Tasks

- Creating SPA applications that are mobile first design with Front end and Back end.

Software Support

Accusoft

03/2020 - 08/2020

Tampa, Florida

St Petersburg

Accusoft is a software development company specializing in content processing, conversion, and automation. We enable users to solve content challenaes

Achievements/Tasks

- Problem solving bugs and errors that come in from our internal database or code
- Writing C# and SQL queries to accomplish tasks at hand
- Reproducing issues to help better determine the cause of the problem.

CBTS/Parkbench ODIN Portal contract B-Lynk

07/2020 - 08/2020 B-Lynk

St Petersbura

Achievements/Tasks

- Worked with One other developer from B-Lynk to rebase code, utilize github to make pull and push requests between the different branches of code, and worked directly with Parkbench and CBTS devs.
- Restructured and recoded many portions of the website in react and had to work on some components that were in angular

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer bootcamp

Suncoast Developers Guild

07/2019 - 10/2019

St Petersburg, Florida

High School Education IMG Academy

06/2018 - 01/2019

Bradenton, Florida

SKILLS



PROJECTS

Weather App 🗹

Working weather app pulling from external API (React)

Productivity Suite 🗹

Multifunction SPA application that allows you to keep track and mark important events in calendar, keep track of thoughts and notes in journal based on color coordination, and use the To-Do list to keep track of your day to day tasks. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, C#, .Net, Postgres)

Employee Database 🗹

- Employee Database app using external API to hold and store information. (React)

Recipe Website 🗹

Useful website for getting healthy recipes to cook with.

Portfolio Website 🗹

Portfolio Website to get linked to all of my important links such as github, LinkedIn.

INTERESTS

